m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Silver Wolf  Lv.158
Skills [Sharp Fangs]
Skills [Reflexes (Grade C)]
Skills [Agility (Grade C)]
Skills Leadership
#08 "A Little Girl's Wish"
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Dryade    Lv.55
Skills [Forest Sensitivity]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Golden Bee  Lv.256
Skills [High-Speed Flight] [Intense Stinger]
Skills [Slash Resistance (Grade C)]
Skills [Blunt Force Resistance (Grade C)] [Magic Absorption]
Noir
7th Floor Again
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Target
Allows hostile enemies
to target the skill
holder more easily.
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Target
Allows hostile enemies
to target the skill
holder more easily.
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Target
Allows hostile enemies
to target the skill
holder more easily.
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Target
Allows hostile enemies to
target the skill holder more
easily, especially by Silver
Wolves, who will consider
it their natural enemy.
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Whatcha think?
Water Drop
Creates a drop of fresh water.
Droplets may be fired.
Creates a drop of fresh
or sea water.
Droplets may be fired.
Wind Selection
Grade A
Fruitful Drop
Grade AAA
Alice Theater
#09 "To the Gala"
Illustration: Kiseri Matsumiya